Now, the next obvious thing we need to do is make this screen look a little bit better by
下一步的任务很明显 我们将使这个屏幕看起来更棒
connecting the screen to read X and then going and grabbing the day for the specific key.
将此屏幕连接到 Redux 然后获取特定键对应的日期的信息
So what we'll do is inside of entry details,
转到 EntryDetail.js 文件
go ahead and import some things.
导入一些内容
We will add some style so import style sheets.
我们将添加一些样式 因此导入 StyleSheet
We will also import connect and then because we're here,
还需要导入 connect
let's also import the color whites.
趁机导入颜色 white
All right, so now what we want to do is instead of exporting entry detail.
在这里 我们不再导出 EntryDetail
We want to export connect.
而是导出 connect
And then now, let's go ahead and build out our map state to props function right here.
然后在这里构建 mapStateToProps 函数
So we get past the state but we also get past
传入 state
the current props which has a navigation property on it.
还需要传入具有 navigation 属性的当前属性
And then here what we want to do,
然后在这里
is let's grab that entryId that we're getting when we route to entry detail.
获取转到 EntryDetail 视图时所获的 entryId
We can grab that from navigation.state.params and then
我们可以从 navigation.state.params 中获取该 ID
now what we want to return or the information that we want to pass to our component is,
然后返回要传递给组件的所有信息
and go ahead and pass it the entryId.
向其传递 entryId
And then we can also pass it the metrics which is going to
然后传递 metrics
be state at whatever this entryId is.
设为该 entryId 对应的状态
So what we're saying is the entryId is going to be the key of the specific day.
entryId 将为特定日期的键
And so we are passing that to the component but we're also passing
将该 entryId 传递给组件
the specific information about that day under the metrics prop.
同时传递 metrics 属性下关于这一天的具体信息
So now, inside of our entry detail component,
现在转到 EntryDetail 组件下
let's go ahead and grab these metrics off of props.
从属性下获取这些 metrics
And then what we can do is if you remember,
然后我们将...
we created this nice little metric card component that
记得我们创建了这个 MetricCard 组件
is really the UI for this card right here.
表示这个卡片 UI
So let's go ahead and render that as well.
我们也渲染下该卡片
So inside of here,
在这里导入 MetricCard
let's import metric card and then we can render one of those passing it the metrics.
然后渲染其中一个卡片 传入 metrics
And then now before we forget,
在忘记之前
let's go ahead and create some styles here just for our container.
在这里为容器创建一些样式
So we will have, let's say,
输入 container：
container flex of one as always,
和往常一样 flex: 1
we'll say background color is going to be white and then we'll just give
backgroundColor 为 white
it a padding of 15 and this is going to go on this year right here.
将 padding 设为 15 在这个视图中进行设置
So this is looking pretty good.
看起来不错
Let's not forget to pass maps state to props to our connecting location down here.
别忘了在这个 connect 函数中传入 mapsStateToProps
So now what should happen is if everything is working correctly,
如果一切正常的话
when we click on this,
点击这个
we now get this UI right here.
就会转到这个用户界面